[Music]
I mean I guess I just don't want to feel
like I'm being censored in front of a
client no no no and I don't want you to
feel that way I was just feeling a
little off cuz I kept forgetting to call
the fat kids husky that was so funny I
mean you always call them fat that's
what they
are where is
Sheila Tim finally a mysty
yes mystery solved
give me a a box of those pens I like set
me up with a massage at 2:00 and see if
you can get a hold of amelo have him
come over and measure me for some new
suits you got it big
hanang hey
Dad Tim Sam they let you out of The Nut
House yeah got released this
[Music]
morning I'm
back you ain't
never said I was well you've implied
it
from